{"result":[{"team":"Chelsea","question":"Stanford Bridge was first acquired in what year?","option1":"1900","option2":"1896","option3":"1911","answer":"1904","level":"hard"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"How many premier league titles do Chelsea have(First and Second division)?","option1":"5","option2":"6","option3":"7","answer":"8","level":"medium"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"Who has the most goals for Chelsea`","option1":"Ron Harris","option2":"John Hollins","option3":"Steve Clark","answer":"Frank Lampard","level":"easy"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"Frank Lampard has a total of how many goals for Chelsea","option1":"254","option2":"170","option3":"188","answer":"211","level":"hard"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"How many Community Shield do Chelsea own?","option1":"6","option2":"7","option3":"3","answer":"4","level":"medium"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"The youngest player that ever played for Chelsea was how old?","option1":"14","option2":"19","option3":"15","answer":"16","level":"medium"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"What is Chelsea's record win?","option1":"9-1","option2":"6-0","option3":"18-2","answer":"13-0","level":"medium"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"Kepa Arrizabalaga was transferred to Chelsea from what club?","option1":"Napoli","option2":"Marseille","option3":"Monaco","answer":"Athletic Bilbao","level":"easy"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"What year did Chelsea concede the least amount of goals","option1":"02\/03","option2":"1989\/1990","option3":"07\/08","answer":"04\/05","level":"medium"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":" Which of these have never played for Chelsea?","option1":"Frank Lampard ","option2":"Juan Mata","option3":"Michael Essien","answer":"Kevin Dujin","level":"easy"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"Which of these never played for Chelsea?","option1":"Alvaro Morata","option2":"Michy Batshuayi","option3":"Davide Zappacosta","answer":"Robert Picazo","level":"easy"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"Which of these never played for Chelsea?","option1":"Gary Cahill","option2":"Petr Cech","option3":"Joe Cole","answer":"Dusan Tadic","level":"easy"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"Which of these never played for Chelsea?","option1":"Hudson-Odoi","option2":"N'golo Kante","option3":"John Terry","answer":"Lionel Messi","level":"easy"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"Which of these never played for Chelsea?","option1":"Andy Townsend","option2":"Steve Clarke","option3":"Mark Hughes","answer":"Eric Bumps","level":"easy"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"Frank Lampard won player of the year how many times in Chelsea?","option1":"4","option2":"2","option3":"0","answer":"3","level":"easy"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"Antonio Conte first became a Chelsea manager in what year?","option1":"2015","option2":"2017","option3":"2010","answer":"2016","level":"easy"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"Who is Chelsea's head coach of 2018\/19?","option1":"Micky Droy","option2":"Antonio Conte","option3":"Eden Hazard","answer":"Maurizio Sarri","level":"easy"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"Chelsea won their last champion's league in what year?","option1":"10\/11","option2":"14\/15","option3":"12\/13","answer":"11\/12","level":"easy"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"Which of these never played for Chelsea?","option1":"Gonzalo Higuain","option2":"Charly Musonda","option3":"Victor Moses","answer":"Robert Lewandowski","level":"easy"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"Which of these never played for Chelsea?","option1":"Danny Drinkwater","option2":"Andreas Christensen","option3":"Cesar Azpilicueta","answer":"Marco Veratti","level":"easy"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"Which of these never played for Chelsea?","option1":"Kenedy","option2":"Didier Drogba","option3":"Diego Costa","answer":"Jeremy Anelka","level":"easy"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"Which of these never played for Chelsea?","option1":"Nicolas Anelka","option2":"Fernando Torres","option3":"Gianfranco Zola","answer":"Mark Noble","level":"easy"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"Who has the most appearances in total for Chelsea?","option1":"John Hollins","option2":"Frank Lampard","option3":"Mark Hughes","answer":"Ron Harris","level":"medium"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"The first team Chelsea ever played with was?","option1":"Tottenham","option2":"Portsmouth","option3":"Millwall","answer":"Stockport County","level":"hard"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"Chelsea's home stadium is ?","option1":"Stanford Bridge","option2":"London Bridge","option3":"Blue Bridge","answer":"Stamford Bridge","level":"easy"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"Chelsea's kit has been manufactured by ___ since 2017","option1":"Adidas","option2":"Emirates","option3":"Kappa","answer":"Nike","level":"easy"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"Which of these never played for Chelsea?","option1":"Romelu Lukaku","option2":"Nemanja Matic","option3":"Arjen Robben","answer":"Harry Winks","level":"easy"},{"team":"Chelsea","question":"Barcelona has how many Champions league title","option1":"8","option2":"4","option3":"3","answer":"5","level":"medium"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"Barcelona initially played in what stadium ?","option1":"Camp seria","option2":"Camp Acedo","option3":"Camp de Les Cortes","answer":"Camp de La Industria","level":"medium"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"As at 2017\/2018,Barcelona has how mnay league titles","option1":"20","option2":"21","option3":"23","answer":"25","level":"medium"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"Who is Barcelona's all time goal scorer","option1":"Paulino","option2":"Ronaldinho","option3":"Pelle","answer":"Messi","level":"easy"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"Which of these never played for Barcelona?","option1":"Samuel Eto'o","option2":"Luis Suarez","option3":"Andres Iniesta","answer":"Tiago Alcantara","level":"easy"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"Pep Guardiola had a total of how many trophies in 4years","option1":"12","option2":"10","option3":"8","answer":"14","level":"medium"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"Which of these never played for Barcelona?","option1":"Arturo Vidal","option2":"Sergi Roberto","option3":"Nelson Semedo","answer":"Kylian Mbappe","level":"easy"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"Which of these never played for Barcelona?\r\n","option1":"Lionel Messi","option2":"Arthur","option3":"Kevin-prince Boateng","answer":"Emre Can","level":"easy"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"Which of these never played for Barcelona?","option1":"Clement Lenglet","option2":"Arda Turan","option3":"Neymar jr","answer":"Mario Icardy","level":"easy"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"Which of these never played for Barcelona?","option1":"Ronaldinho","option2":"Edgar Davids","option3":"Carles Puyol","answer":"Semen Diola","level":"easy"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"Who is the head coach of Barcelona as at 18\/19 season?","option1":"Juanjo Brau","option2":"Joan Barbara","option3":"Lionel Messi","answer":"Ernesto Valverde","level":"easy"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"Which of these never played for Barcelona?","option1":"Ivan Rakitic","option2":"Jean-Clair Todibo","option3":"Thomas Vermelean","answer":"Thiago Douglass","level":"easy"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"The current club president of Barcelona as at 18\/19 season is ?","option1":"Jordi Cardona","option2":"Didac Lee","option3":"Antonio Guarero","answer":"Josep Mario Bartomeu","level":"hard"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"The highest transfer fee to Barcelona is for what player","option1":"Neymar","option2":"Vidal","option3":"Suarez","answer":"Coutinho","level":"easy"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"Which of these never played for Barcelona?","option1":"Pedro","option2":"Malcom","option3":"Xavi","answer":"Ramos","level":"easy"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"Barcelona current sub sponsor for their shirts is","option1":"Qatar","option2":"Kappa","option3":"Nike","answer":"BEKO & UNICEF","level":"easy"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"Which of these is currently a goalkeeper in Barcelona","option1":"Ousmanne","option2":"Calidion","option3":"Murillio","answer":"Cillessen","level":"easy"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"Who held the record for highest goalscorer for Barcelona before Lionel Messi","option1":"Laszlo Kubala","option2":"Josep Samitier","option3":"Cesar","answer":"Paulino Alcantara","level":"medium"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"Who is Barcelona's longest serving manager ","option1":"John Storm","option2":"Jack Stanways","option3":"Eulogio Martinez","answer":"Jack Greenwell","level":"hard"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"Andres Iniesta has how many trophies in Barcelona(range)","option1":"15-20","option2":"25-30","option3":"30-35","answer":"35-40","level":"medium"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"Who holds the record for most appearances for Barcelona","option1":"Iniesta","option2":"Messi","option3":"Gamper","answer":"Xavi","level":"medium"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"Which of these never played for Barcelona?","option1":"Cesc Fabregas","option2":"Deco","option3":"Belleti","answer":"Ariano Douglas lee","level":"easy"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"Which of these never played for Barcelona?","option1":"Oriol Romerou","option2":"Pedro","option3":"Quaresma","answer":"Di Maria","level":"easy"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"Which of these never played for Barcelona?","option1":"Theirry Henry","option2":"Henrique","option3":"Claudio Bravo","answer":"Musonda Sr","level":"easy"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"Which of these never played for Barcelona?","option1":"Yerry Mina","option2":"Carles Puyol","option3":"Zlatan Ibrahimovic","answer":"Ramsey","level":"easy"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"Which of these never played for Barcelona?","option1":"Alexis Sanchez","option2":"Thiago Motta","option3":"Paulinho","answer":"John Terry","level":"easy"},{"team":"Barcelona","question":"Which of these never played for Barcelona?","option1":"Ronaldo(Brazillian)","option2":"Julio Cesar Romero","option3":"Malcom","answer":"Maximilliano Cuandrengo","level":"easy"}]}